Bavarian	B-LOC
Soviet	I-LOC
Republic	I-LOC

**	O
starting	O
26	O
December	O
:	O
Long	B-PER
Boret	I-PER

T315I-positive	O
Chronic	B-ORG
myelogenous	I-ORG
leukaemia	I-ORG
and	O
Acute	B-ORG
lymphoblastic	I-ORG
leukaemia	I-ORG
