'	O
''	O
Louisville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kentucky	I-LOC
''	O
'	O

``	O
Aku	B-ORG
Memilih	I-ORG
Setia	I-ORG
''	O

Manchukuo	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG

16	O
-	O
Tony	B-PER
Hall	I-PER

Jarrod	B-PER
Saltalamacchia	I-PER
(	O
2006–2007	O
)	O

A	O
typical	O
example	O
is	O
Earith	B-LOC
Bulwark	I-LOC
