''	O
Kansas	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Jerry	B-PER
Leiber	I-PER
,	O
Mike	B-PER
Stoller	I-PER
)	O

In	O
2010	O
,	O
he	O
signed	O
to	O
the	O
newly	O
formed	O
G-Note	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
subsidiary	O
label	O
of	O
50	B-PER
Cent	I-PER
's	O
G-Unit	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
.	O

''	O
November	O
23	O
''	O
–	O
The	B-PER
Hitchhiker	I-PER

São	B-LOC
Caetano	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pernambuco	I-LOC

Portuguese	B-ORG
legislative	I-ORG
election	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
2015	I-ORG

''	O
Mamluk	B-LOC
Sultanate	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Egypt	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
–	O
Barsbay	B-PER
(	O
1422–1437	O
)	O

Harrah	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Casino	I-LOC
Tunica	I-LOC

Jacques	B-PER
Roumain	I-PER
(	O
1907–1944	O
)	O
