''	O
Infurcitinea	B-LOC
argentimaculella	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Stainton	O
,	O
1849	O
)	O

The	O
same	O
year	O
he	O
was	O
offered	O
a	O
contract	O
to	O
Jermaine	B-PER
Dupri	I-PER
's	O
So	B-ORG
So	B-ORG
Def	I-ORG
label	O
.	O
