''As	O
of	O
UAE	B-ORG
Pro	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
:	O
''	O

John	B-PER
III	I-PER
Sobieski	I-PER

10	B-ORG
June	I-ORG
2013	I-ORG
Iraq	I-ORG
attacks	I-ORG

Daniel	B-PER
Black	I-PER
Chisholm	I-PER
-	O
1871–1872	O

''	O
Syncopacma	B-LOC
polychromella	I-LOC
''	O
