``	O
Think	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Minute	I-ORG
''	O

``	O
The	B-LOC
Queen	I-LOC
and	I-LOC
I	I-LOC
''	O
—	O
3:15	O

Michael	B-PER
Jackson	I-PER
—	O
``	O
Thriller	B-ORG
''	O
