Walter	B-PER
B.	I-PER
Woodbury	I-PER

United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
:	O
Henry	B-PER
Wadsworth	I-PER
Longfellow	I-PER
,	O
Ralph	B-PER
Waldo	I-PER
Emerson	I-PER
,	O
Edgar	B-PER
Allan	I-PER
Poe	I-PER

Longfellow	B-ORG
Bridge	I-ORG
,	O
Boston	B-LOC
/	O
Cambridge	B-LOC

He	O
was	O
born	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
Carton	B-LOC
House	I-LOC
.	O

Label	O
:	O
Universal	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
Records	I-ORG
