``	O
Flaunt	B-ORG
It	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
TV	B-ORG
Rock	I-ORG
featuring	O
Seany	B-PER
B	I-PER
(	O
4	O
weeks	O
)	O

Number	B-ORG
10	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
series	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

2014	O
:	O
First	O
round	O
(	O
lost	O
to	O
Mervyn	B-PER
King	I-PER
0–3	O
)	O

25px	O
Helvetic	B-LOC
Republic	I-LOC
-	O
1,600,000	O

Judyty	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pomeranian	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC
