2000	B-ORG
Men	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
Olympic	I-ORG
Games	I-ORG
100m	I-ORG
Breaststroke	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Sydney	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

All	B-ORG
Star	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
song	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

*1967	O
:	O
honorary	O
Doctor	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Laws	I-ORG
from	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Manitoba	I-ORG

Mary	B-PER
of	I-PER
the	I-PER
Divine	I-PER
Heart	I-PER

'	O
''	O
Winnipeg	B-ORG
Blue	I-ORG
Bombers	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Reserve	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Parke	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Indiana	I-LOC

Initially	O
,	O
the	O
band	O
featured	O
BJH	O
drummer	O
Mel	B-PER
Pritchard	I-PER
.	O

''	O
Parmelia	B-LOC
asiatica	I-LOC
''	O

Hampden	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Massachusetts	I-LOC

''	O
Ancylolomia	B-LOC
inornata	I-LOC
''	O
Staudinger	O
,	O
1870	O

Ha	B-PER
Jung-woo	I-PER
,	O
Kang	B-PER
Dong-won	I-PER
