'	O
''	O
Wayne	B-PER
Black	I-PER
''	O
'	O
'	O
''	O
Brian	B-PER
MacPhie	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Channel	B-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
,	O

In	O
1994	O
,	O
the	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Times	I-ORG
''	O
wrote	O
he	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
voted	O
the	O
``	O
best-known	O
artist	O
of	O
the	O
century	O
''	O
.	O
