**London	O
:	O
Thames	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Hudson	I-ORG
.	O

''Also	O
see	O
:	O
Hot	B-ORG
100	I-ORG
No.	I-ORG
1	I-ORG
Hits	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
1979	I-ORG
''	O

Jean-Baptiste	B-PER
Stouf	I-PER
(	O
1785	O
)	O

India	B-LOC
(	O
Uttar	B-LOC
Pradesh	I-LOC
)	O

Mount	B-LOC
Airy	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Louisiana	I-LOC

''	O
Stagmatoptera	B-LOC
abdominalis	I-LOC
''	O

Lancaster	B-ORG
Independent	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
District	I-ORG

*Minister-President	O
of	O
Thuringia	B-LOC
–	O
Dieter	B-PER
Althaus	I-PER

Bethesda	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Maryland	I-LOC
,	O
U.S	B-ORG
.	I-ORG

Reg	B-PER
Baker	I-PER
(	O
1899–	O
?	O

'	O
''	O
With	O
Stan	B-PER
Kenton	I-PER
''	O
'	O
