Blaze	B-PER
Ya	I-PER
Dead	I-PER
Homie	I-PER
-	O
(	O
9	O
)	O

Franklin	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	O
Eastpoint	B-LOC

Mirko	B-PER
and	I-PER
Stjepan	I-PER
Seljan	I-PER

''	O
Mamluk	B-LOC
Sultanate	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Egypt	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
–	O
Barsbay	B-PER
(	O
1422–1437	O
)	O

McKean	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC

1887	O
first	O
elected	O
in	O
1935	O
as	O
Social	B-ORG
Credit	I-ORG
member	O
for	O
Vegreville	B-LOC
,	O
Alberta	B-LOC
.	O
