Takashi	B-PER
Ukaji	I-PER
as	O
Akira	B-PER
Kurosawa	I-PER

SWAT	B-ORG
Kats	I-ORG
:	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Radical	I-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG

Paradise	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
The	I-LOC
Insyderz	I-LOC
EP	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

''	O
Jung	B-PER
Woo	I-PER
''	O
'	O
-	O
'	O
''	O
You	B-ORG
're	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Best	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Lee	I-ORG
Soon-shin	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
''	O

It	O
is	O
officially	O
recognized	O
in	O
Russia	B-LOC
.	O

Luke	B-PER
Ridnour	I-PER
(	O
6	O
)	O

Jaquirana	B-LOC
Remo	I-LOC
language	I-LOC

Unionville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Chester	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC

North-West	B-ORG
Mounted	I-ORG
Police	I-ORG

Alim	B-PER
Kouliev	I-PER
-	O
''Urka	O
''	O
