'	O
''	O
Louisville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kentucky	I-LOC
''	O
'	O

San	B-LOC
Juan	I-LOC
y	I-LOC
Martínez	I-LOC

''	O
Up	B-ORG
On	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Ridge	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
Dierks	B-PER
Bentley	I-PER

Emerald	B-ORG
Tower	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Brisbane	I-ORG

Jane	B-PER
Bown	I-PER
-	O
Lifetime	O
Achievement	O

Manchukuo	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Force	I-ORG

16	O
-	O
Tony	B-PER
Hall	I-PER

He	O
joined	O
Newton	B-ORG
Heath	I-ORG
in	O
February	O
1899	O
as	O
a	O
replacement	O
for	O
James	B-PER
McNaught	I-PER
.	O

Idahlu	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Hamadan	I-LOC

A	O
typical	O
example	O
is	O
Earith	B-LOC
Bulwark	I-LOC
