William	B-PER
O'Connor	I-PER
''	O
(	O
First	O
round	O
)	O

Osseo	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Minnesota	I-LOC
–	O
$	O
23,507	O

Granada	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Colorado	I-LOC

They	O
also	O
describe	O
his	O
trips	O
to	O
North	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
and	O
Greece	B-LOC
.	O

'	O
''	O
Felicia	B-PER
Day	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Gene	B-PER
Autry	I-PER
and	O
Oakley	B-PER
Haldeman	I-PER

Science	B-ORG
Fiction	I-ORG
Quarterly	I-ORG
''	O
,	O
1940–1943	O
,	O
10	O
issues	O
,	O
revived	O
1951–1958	O

*2010	O
:	O
``	O
Your	B-ORG
Love	I-ORG
Is	I-ORG
My	I-ORG
Drug	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Ke	B-ORG
$	I-ORG
ha	I-ORG
)	O
'	O
''	O
1	O
''	O
'	O

College	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
DuPage	I-ORG
(	O
Glen	B-LOC
Ellyn	I-LOC
)	O
