Whitney	B-PER
Houston	I-PER
–	O
``	O
How	B-ORG
Will	I-ORG
I	I-ORG
Know	I-ORG
''	O

''	O
Lathyrus	B-LOC
aphaca	I-LOC
''	O
L	O
.	O
