It	O
is	O
also	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Juan	B-LOC
Fernández	I-LOC
Islands	I-LOC
.	O

Robert	B-PER
T.	I-PER
A.	I-PER
Innes	I-PER

William	B-PER
C.	I-PER
Gorgas	I-PER

List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Zeppelins	I-ORG

Parañaque	B-LOC
,	O
Metro	B-LOC
Manila	I-LOC
,	O
Philippines	B-LOC
