Derick	B-ORG
Thompson	I-ORG
(	O
unknown	O
)	O

''	O
'Ireland	O
''	O
'	O
-	O
Máel	B-PER
Sechnaill	I-PER
mac	I-PER
Domnaill	I-PER
,	O
High	B-PER
King	I-PER
of	I-PER
Ireland	I-PER
(	O
1014–1022	O
)	O

Will	B-PER
Ferrell	I-PER
,	O
Caroline	B-PER
Rhea	I-PER

Bad	B-ORG
Education	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
TV	I-ORG
series	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Zane	B-PER
Lowe	I-PER
:	O
November	O
3	O
,	O
2008	O

BUS	B-ORG
US	I-ORG
10	I-ORG
–	O
Midland	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Michigan	I-LOC

Pink	B-PER
(	O
8	O
)	O

'	O
''	O
Coppery-chested	B-LOC
jacamar	I-LOC
''	O
'	O

Polynesian	B-LOC
longfinned	I-LOC
eel	I-LOC

Texas	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Highway	I-ORG
316	I-ORG

''	O
Ephestia	B-ORG
kuehniella	I-ORG
''	O
Zeller	O
,	O
1879	O

'	O
''	O
Neil	B-PER
Symes	I-PER
''	O
'	O
