``	O
Pumped	B-ORG
Up	I-ORG
Kicks	I-ORG
''	O

Won	O
the	O
African	B-ORG
Champions	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
once	O
with	O
JS	B-ORG
Kabylie	I-ORG
in	O
1990	O

Guido	B-PER
De	I-PER
Luigi	I-PER

=	O
Riccardia	B-LOC
chamedryfolia	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
With	O
.	O
