Lohan	B-PER
Jacobs	I-PER
(	O
released	O
)	O

Working	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG
on	I-ORG
Indigenous	I-ORG
Populations	I-ORG

Similar	O
deals	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
plants	O
in	O
Vancouver	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
,	O
Canada	B-LOC
and	O
the	O
Orange	B-ORG
Free	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
,	O
South	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
same	O
year	O
.	O
