History	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Western	I-LOC
Australia	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
With	O
Art	B-PER
Farmer	I-PER
''	O
'	O

''	O
Monochroa	B-LOC
arundinetella	I-LOC
''	O
(	O
Stainton	O
,	O
1858	O
)	O

Party	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Regions	I-ORG
,	O
№	O
166	O

Jodi	B-PER
Albert	I-PER
(	O
Debbie	B-PER
Dean	I-PER
)	O
