George	B-PER
Harrison	I-PER
–	O
guitar	O
lead	O
,	O
hát	O
nền	O
.	O

Bochnia	B-LOC
,	O
Ba	B-LOC
Lan	I-LOC

''Stars	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Stripes	I-ORG
''	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
báo	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
