2,000	B-ORG
Guineas	I-ORG
Stakes	I-ORG
–	O
El	B-LOC
Gran	I-LOC
Senor	I-LOC

Superior	B-LOC
ganglion	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
vagus	I-LOC
nerve	I-LOC

It	O
is	O
close	O
to	O
St	B-ORG
Albans	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
railway	I-ORG
station	I-ORG
.	O

Richard	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Daley	I-PER
-	O
2	O
(	O
0.07	O
%	O
)	O

Kevin	B-PER
Garnett	I-PER
(	O
12	O
)	O
