Sergey	B-PER
Shoygu	I-PER
(	O
2012	O
)	O

He	O
was	O
named	O
to	O
the	O
second-team	O
Big	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
along	O
with	O
Tyvon	B-PER
Branch	I-PER
.	O

Blue	B-ORG
Grass	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
—	O
Lexington	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kentucky	I-LOC

It	O
is	O
served	O
by	O
Landywood	B-ORG
railway	I-ORG
station	I-ORG
on	O
the	O
Chase	B-ORG
Line	I-ORG
,	O
which	O
runs	O
from	O
Birmingham	B-LOC
via	O
Walsall	B-LOC
to	O
Rugeley	B-ORG
Trent	I-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
.	O
