51	O
,	O
Probolinggo	B-LOC
,	O
East	B-LOC
Java	I-LOC

Bobirwa	B-LOC
,	O
headquarters	O
at	O
Bobonong	B-LOC

New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Tisch	I-ORG
Hospital	I-ORG
,	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC

Gladstone	B-ORG
Dock	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
LOR	I-ORG
)	I-ORG
railway	I-ORG
station	I-ORG

Mansheyat	B-ORG
Bani	I-ORG
Hasan	I-ORG

Tom	B-PER
Hollander	I-PER
(	O
1992	O
)	O
,	O
for	O
Witwoud	O
in	O
The	B-ORG
Way	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
World	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Lyric	B-ORG
Hammersmith	I-ORG
)	O

'	O
''	O
W	O
''	O
'	O
:	O
Duane	B-PER
Ward	I-PER
(	O
1-0	O
)	O
''	O
'L	O
''	O
'	O
:	O
Kelly	B-PER
Downs	I-PER
(	O
0-1	O
)	O
''	O
'S	O
''	O
'	O
:	O
Tom	B-PER
Henke	I-PER
(	O
3	O
)	O

''	O
Back	B-PER
Of	I-PER
The	I-PER
Y	I-PER
''	O

Emperor	B-PER
Tsuchimikado	I-PER
succeeds	O
Emperor	B-PER
Go-Toba	I-PER
on	O
the	O
throne	O
of	O
Japan	B-LOC
.	O

''	O
Salvia	B-LOC
whitehousei	I-LOC
''	O
Alziar	O
