*1967	O
:	O
honorary	O
Doctor	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Laws	I-ORG
from	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Manitoba	I-ORG

Dupuis	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Jacques	I-ORG
.	O

Initially	O
,	O
the	O
band	O
featured	O
BJH	O
drummer	O
Mel	B-PER
Pritchard	I-PER
.	O

Jeníkov	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
Teplice	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Emirate	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Tbilisi	I-LOC
