'	O
''	O
Daniel	B-PER
Arap	I-PER
Moi	I-PER
''	O
'	O
(	O
1924–	O
)	O

Eneo	O
lake	O
ni	O
7.7	O
km²	B-ORG
.	O

Spring	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC

What	B-ORG
Makes	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Man	I-ORG

Papa	B-PER
Innocent	I-PER
V	I-PER

Ni	O
pia	O
jina	O
la	O
Bahari	B-LOC
Nyeusi	I-LOC
.	O

Do	B-ORG
n't	I-ORG
Stop	I-ORG
'til	I-ORG
You	I-ORG
Get	I-ORG
Enough	I-ORG
-	O
6:02	O
