Musa	B-PER
Haji	I-PER
Ismail	I-PER
Galal	I-PER

Lower	B-LOC
West	I-LOC
Pubnico	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Nova	I-LOC
Scotia	I-LOC

Whatcom	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Washington	I-LOC

New	B-LOC
Westminster	I-LOC
,	O
British	B-LOC
Columbia	I-LOC

Countdown	B-LOC
:	I-LOC
The	I-LOC
Savoy	I-LOC
Sessions	I-LOC
''	O

Friedrich	B-PER
Heinrich	I-PER
Vering	I-PER
(	O
1833–1896	O
)	O

Kootenay	B-ORG
Ice	I-ORG
''	O
'x	O
''	O
'	O

Before	O
1945	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Germany	B-LOC
.	O

'	O
''	O
Milton	B-ORG
Keynes	I-ORG
Lions	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

R.J.	B-PER
Rummel	I-PER
(	O
1990	O
)	O
.	O

Wanya	B-PER
Morris	I-PER
of	O
Boyz	B-ORG
II	I-ORG
Men	I-ORG

Co-written	O
with	O
Adam	B-ORG
E.	I-ORG
Fierro	I-ORG
