Jean-Baptiste	B-PER
Stouf	I-PER
(	O
1785	O
)	O

India	B-LOC
(	O
Uttar	B-LOC
Pradesh	I-LOC
)	O

Eurasian	B-LOC
jay	I-LOC
,	O
''Garrulus	O
glandarius	O
''	O

``	O
Dancing	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Street	I-ORG
''	O
quickly	O
went	O
to	O
number	O
one	O
on	O
release	O
.	O

Lancaster	B-ORG
Independent	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
District	I-ORG

Reg	B-PER
Baker	I-PER
(	O
1899–	O
?	O
