National	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Western	I-ORG
Australia	I-ORG

Red-winged	B-LOC
grey	I-LOC
warbler	I-LOC

Ardrossan]]	O
,	O
)	O
Strathcona	B-LOC
County	I-LOC

Flashlight	B-ORG
Brown	I-ORG
(	O
inactive	O
)	O

East	B-LOC
St.	I-LOC
Louis	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Illinois	I-LOC

''	O
Thames	B-ORG
TV	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Billy	B-PER
Gilbert	I-PER
,	O
2B	O
,	O
1908-1909	O

Chris	B-ORG
Milburn	I-ORG
(	O
Sydney—Victoria	B-LOC
)	O
===	O

Khanpur	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Uttar	I-LOC
Pradesh	I-LOC

Yvonne	B-PER
Strahovski	I-PER
–	O
Chuck	B-ORG
''	O

Joseph	B-PER
Bonomi	I-PER
the	I-PER
Younger	I-PER

''	O
Stretching	O
''	O
by	O
Art	B-PER
Blakey	I-PER
