Judge	B-PER
Reinhold	I-PER
,	O
Fred	B-PER
Savage	I-PER

Francesco	B-PER
Botticini	I-PER
or	O
Andrea	B-ORG
Castagna	I-ORG

John	B-PER
Randolph	I-PER
Tucker	I-PER
(	I-PER
politician	I-PER
)	I-PER

*Strange	O
''	O
(	O
from	O
Hellbound	B-ORG
)	O
''	O

''	O
Papilio	B-LOC
thuraui	I-LOC
''	O
Karsch	O
,	O
1900	O

*2006-09-10	O
:	O
119,0	O
m	O
-	O
Tobias	B-PER
Bogner	I-PER
,	O
Germany	B-LOC

Durhamville	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
disambiguation	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Hazel	B-LOC
Green	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Alabama	I-LOC
$	O
18,397	O

'	O
''	O
KV20	B-ORG
''	O
'	O

McMinn	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Tennessee	I-LOC

St.	B-ORG
Paul	I-ORG
's	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Macau	I-ORG

''	O
Union	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
''	O
'	O
