Choctaw	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Alabama	I-LOC

Jean	B-PER
De	I-PER
Briac	I-PER
-	O
Shopkeeper	O

'	O
''	O
Marianne	B-PER
Thieme	I-PER
''	O
'	O

**	O
Sgùrr	B-LOC
a	I-LOC
'	I-LOC
Ghreadaidh	I-LOC
(	O
973	O
m	O
)	O

It	O
is	O
the	O
site	O
name	O
for	O
the	O
Saqqaq	B-ORG
culture	I-ORG
.	O

We	B-ORG
Like	I-ORG
to	I-ORG
Rock	I-ORG
