**	O
''	O
Paracymoriza	B-LOC
albimaculata	I-LOC
''	O
F.Q	O
.	O

Famous	O
names	O
have	O
performed	O
there	O
including	O
:	O
Edith	B-ORG
Piaf	I-ORG
,	O
Siegfried	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Roy	I-ORG
,	O
Sylvie	B-PER
Vartan	I-PER
,	O
Johnny	B-PER
Hallyday	I-PER
,	O
Maurice	B-PER
Chevalier	I-PER
,	O
Marlene	B-PER
Dietrich	I-PER
,	O
Eartha	B-PER
Kitt	I-PER
,	O
Josephine	B-PER
Baker	I-PER
,	O
Kessler	B-PER
Twins	I-PER
,	O
Elton	B-PER
John	I-PER
,	O
Laurel	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Hardy	I-ORG
,	O
Dalida	B-PER
,	O
Shirley	B-PER
MacLaine	I-PER
,	O
Mitzi	B-PER
Gaynor	I-PER
,	O
Juliet	B-PER
Prowse	I-PER
and	O
Noël	B-PER
Coward	I-PER
.	O
