She	O
and	O
other	O
dancers	O
were	O
photographed	O
by	O
artist	O
Edmund	B-PER
Kesting	I-PER
.	O

Black-throated	B-LOC
laughingthrush	I-LOC
,	O
unsuccessfully	O
introduced	O
to	O
the	O
Hawaiian	B-LOC
Islands	I-LOC

''	O
Night	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Day	I-ORG
''	O
-	O
3:58	O
