It	O
is	O
located	O
in	O
Rancho	B-LOC
Cucamonga	I-LOC
.	O

In	O
the	O
Netherlands	B-LOC
,	O
Part	B-ORG
1	I-ORG
was	O
released	O
on	O
June	O
23	O
,	O
2006	O
and	O
Part	B-ORG
2	I-ORG
was	O
released	O
on	O
November	O
17	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
year	O
.	O

Claude	B-PER
R.	I-PER
Kirk	I-PER
,	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
.	I-PER

Łąkociny	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Lower	I-LOC
Silesian	I-LOC
Voivodeship	I-LOC

Rugby	B-ORG
,	I-ORG
Tennessee	I-ORG

The	O
third	O
building	O
was	O
designed	O
by	O
Edward	B-PER
Middleton	I-PER
Barry	I-PER
and	O
opened	O
in	O
1858	O
.	O
