Sparsh	B-PER
Khanchandani	I-PER
-	O
Uttran	B-LOC
''	O
as	O
Ichchha	O

Triceps	B-LOC
brachii	I-LOC
muscle	I-LOC

The	O
calculated	O
Height	B-ORG
Above	I-ORG
Average	I-ORG
Terrain	I-ORG
is	O
.	O

``	O
Boku	B-ORG
wa	I-ORG
Ganbaru	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
by	O
Anna	B-PER
Iriyama	I-PER
,	O
Rina	B-PER
Kawaei	I-PER
,	O
Minami	B-PER
Takahashi	I-PER
,	O
Yui	B-PER
Yokoyama	I-PER
,	O
Mayu	B-PER
Watanabe	I-PER
,	O
Yuko	B-PER
Oshima	I-PER
,	O
Yuki	B-PER
Kashiwagi	I-PER
,	O
Haruna	B-PER
Kojima	I-PER
,	O
Haruka	B-PER
Shimazaki	I-PER
)	O
