'	O
''	O
President	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Cup	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Bishop	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Bath	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Wells	I-ORG

Huayllabamba	B-LOC
(	O
Huayllabamba	B-LOC
)	O

''	O
The	O
Kalmar-Ruby	O
Song	O
Book	O
''	O
Random	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
(	O
1936	O
)	O
B009X7KK6K	O
Introduction	O
by	O
Ben	B-PER
Hecht	I-PER
with	O
contributions	O
by	O
Groucho	B-PER
Marx	I-PER
,	O
Robert	B-PER
Benchley	I-PER
,	O
Moss	B-PER
Hart	I-PER
,	O
Irving	B-PER
Berlin	I-PER
,	O
Marc	B-PER
Connelly	I-PER
,	O
James	B-PER
Kevin	I-PER
McGuinness	I-PER
,	O
Franklin	B-ORG
P.	I-ORG
Adams	I-ORG
and	O
Nunnally	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
.	O

:1st	O
Stage	O
4	O
Giro	B-ORG
d'Italia	I-ORG
,	O
Enrico	B-PER
Battaglin	I-PER

The	O
most	O
recent	O
estimates	O
available	O
suggest	O
there	O
are	O
12	O
occurrences	O
in	O
existence	O
for	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
about	O
278,000	O
individual	O
plants	O
in	O
Delta	B-LOC
and	O
Montrose	B-LOC
Counties	I-LOC
.	O

Bat	B-ORG
Out	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Hell	I-ORG
''	O

William	B-PER
O.	I-PER
Douglas	I-PER
!	O
!	O

Episcopal	B-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Rochester	I-LOC

Sir	B-PER
Robert	I-PER
Douglas	I-PER
,	I-PER
6th	I-PER
Baronet	I-PER

''	O
Phyllocnistis	B-LOC
argothea	I-LOC
''	O
Meyrick	O
,	O
1933	O

