Antonín	B-PER
Rýgr	I-PER
(	O
1970–72	O
)	O

Las	B-LOC
Cruces	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
Mexico	I-LOC

Martha	B-PER
Henry	I-PER
(	O
for	O
acting	O
)	O

Virginia	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Route	I-ORG
231	I-ORG

Long-tailed	B-LOC
ground	I-LOC
roller	I-LOC

Drama	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
''	O
``	O
낙타씨의	O
행방불명	O
''	O
