West	B-LOC
Ukrainian	I-LOC
People	I-LOC
's	I-LOC
Republic	I-LOC

University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Akron	I-ORG
(	O
Akron	B-LOC
)	O

''	O
Kingdom	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
France	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
–	O
Charles	B-PER
IV	I-PER
(	O
1322–1328	O
)	O
