Millonarios	B-ORG
F.C	I-ORG
.	I-ORG

**	O
Lister	B-ORG
Mills	I-ORG
founded	O
in	O
Manningham	B-LOC
.	O

Harrison	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC

Antanas	B-PER
Smetona	I-PER
,	O
Mykolas	B-PER
Biržiška	I-PER
,	O
and	O
Steponas	B-PER
Kairys	I-PER
emigrated	O
to	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
and	O
are	O
buried	O
there	O
.	O

'	O
''	O
FA	B-ORG
Premier	I-ORG
Academy	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Ashley	B-PER
Battle	I-PER
2000	O
,	O
WNBA	B-ORG
player	O
for	O
the	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Liberty	I-ORG

Blacklick	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Cambria	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Pennsylvania	I-LOC

Arcada	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	O
Gratiot	B-LOC
County	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
Irina	B-PER
Buryachok	I-PER
''	O
'	O
'	O
''	O
Oksana	B-PER
Kalashnikova	I-PER
''	O
'4–6	O
,	O
7–6	O
(	O
7–3	O
)	O
,	O
[10–4]	O
