Dysart	B-LOC
et	I-LOC
al	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ontario	I-LOC

He	O
earned	O
a	O
Ph.D.	O
in	O
Peace	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Conflict	I-ORG
Studies	I-ORG
from	O
Uppsala	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
in	O
Uppsala	B-LOC
,	O
Sweden	B-LOC
.	O

Les	B-ORG
Aventures	I-ORG
du	I-ORG
roi	I-ORG
Pausole	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
1933	O
)	O

She	O
is	O
the	O
ex-wife	O
of	O
Stephen	B-PER
Hawking	I-PER
.	O

Julije	B-PER
Knifer	I-PER
(	O
1924–2004	O
)	O
