Eyton	B-LOC
on	I-LOC
Severn	I-LOC

Embassy	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Tanzania	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Beijing	I-ORG

Of	O
those	O
aged	O
16–74	O
,	O
30.2	O
%	O
had	O
no	O
academic	B-ORG
qualifications	I-ORG
.	O

Paoay	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
National	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
-	O
Ilocos	B-LOC
Norte	I-LOC

Tor	B-PER
Henning	I-PER
Hamre	I-PER
(	O
39	O
)	O

The	O
exhibition	O
included	O
work	O
by	O
David	B-PER
Hare	I-PER
,	O
Arshile	B-PER
Gorky	I-PER
,	O
Roberto	B-PER
Matta	I-PER
and	O
Isamu	B-PER
Noguchi	I-PER
.	O

Antiochia	B-LOC
in	I-LOC
Sittacene	I-LOC
–	O
Antiochus	B-PER
I	I-PER
Soter	I-PER

He	O
died	O
aged	O
95	O
in	O
Beijing	B-LOC
,	O
following	O
an	O
illness	O
.	O

He	O
was	O
promoted	O
to	O
his	O
final	O
rank	O
of	O
Air	B-ORG
Vice-Marshal	I-ORG
on	O
4	O
January	O
2005	O
.	O

Michael	B-PER
Doleac	I-PER
–	O
1999	O

Kilmuir	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Easter	I-LOC
Ross	I-LOC

Kosuge	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Tokyo	B-LOC
,	O
Japan	B-LOC
in	O
1983	O
.	O

/	O
255	O
or	O
256	O
Samarra	B-LOC
,	O
Iraq	B-LOC
