2,000	B-ORG
Guineas	I-ORG
Stakes	I-ORG
–	O
El	B-LOC
Gran	I-LOC
Senor	I-LOC

Early	O
customers	O
include	O
City	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
San	I-LOC
Jose	I-LOC
,	O
Autodesk	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
Netflix	B-ORG
.	O

Araguari	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
(	I-LOC
Amapá	I-LOC
)	I-LOC

Mikulić	B-PER
,	I-PER
Branko	I-PER
–	O
(	O
April	O
1982	O
–	O
26	O
April	O
1984	O
)	O

Richard	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Daley	I-PER
-	O
2	O
(	O
0.07	O
%	O
)	O

To	O
Vancouver	B-ORG
Canucks	I-ORG
Peter	B-PER
Zezel	I-PER

Stade	B-ORG
Léo	I-ORG
Lagrange	I-ORG
-	O
Poissy	B-LOC
(	O
Yvelines	B-LOC
)	O

Kevin	B-PER
Garnett	I-PER
(	O
12	O
)	O

Beltzville	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
Park	I-ORG
(	O
Carbon	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
)	O
