Dublin	B-LOC
-	O
''Dublin	O
Airport	O
''	O

Kebbi	B-ORG
(	I-ORG
jimbo	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Pleasant	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
Haile	B-PER
Selassie	I-PER
''	O
'	O
