*14px	O
–	O
North	B-ORG
Hobart	I-ORG
Football	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG

It	O
also	O
borders	O
the	O
Czech	B-LOC
Republic	I-LOC
.	O

Governor	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Georgia	I-ORG
:	O
David	B-PER
Brydie	I-PER
Mitchell	I-PER
(	O
Democratic-Republican	B-ORG
)	O
(	O
until	O
November	O
5	O
)	O
,	O
Peter	B-PER
Early	I-PER
(	O
Democratic-Republican	B-ORG
)	O
(	O
starting	O
November	O
5	O
)	O

''	O
Acrocercops	B-LOC
symmetropa	I-LOC
''	O
Meyrick	O
,	O
1939	O

Safed	B-LOC
,	O
circa	O
1593	O
.	O

Observatorio	B-ORG
de	I-ORG
La	I-ORG
Cañada	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Iván	B-PER
Silva	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Dębina	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Prudnik	I-LOC
County	I-LOC

*On	O
May	O
17	O
,	O
1989	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
eight	O
appearances	O
as	O
a	O
guest	O
on	O
The	B-PER
Arsenio	I-PER
Hall	I-PER
Show	I-PER
over	O
five	O
years	O
.	O

MG	B-ORG
Road	I-ORG
metro	I-ORG
station	I-ORG

Covered	O
in	O
2010	O
by	O
Jason	B-PER
Donovan	I-PER
for	O
his	O
80s	O
covers	O
album	O
Soundtrack	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
80s	I-LOC
''	O
