Dave	B-PER
Righetti	I-PER
(	O
1	O
)	O

Genipa	B-LOC
americana	I-LOC
(	O
''hawa	O
''	O
,	O
''jagua	O
''	O
,	O
''huito	O
''	O
,	O
''genipapo	O
''	O
)	O

West	B-ORG
Texas	I-ORG
A	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
M	I-ORG
University	I-ORG

World	B-ORG
Mental	I-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Day	I-ORG
(	O
International	B-ORG
)	O

Wachenheim	B-ORG
an	I-ORG
der	I-ORG
Weinstraße	I-ORG
(	O
Rhl.-Pf	O
.	O

Tollak	B-PER
B.	I-PER
Sirnes	I-PER

Spirulina	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
genus	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
