Tufted	B-LOC
duck	I-LOC
,	O
''Aythya	O
fuligula	O
''	O

There	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Armed	B-ORG
Resistance	I-ORG
by	O
Jan	B-PER
Nowak-Jeziorański	I-PER
.	O

Communist	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Peoples	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Spain	I-ORG
(	O
PCPE	O
)	O
