Peter	B-PER
T.	I-PER
King	I-PER

Sergey	B-PER
Shoygu	I-PER
(	O
2012	O
)	O

Beginning	O
of	O
Karoo	B-ORG
Ice	I-ORG
Age	I-ORG
.	O

He	O
was	O
named	O
to	O
the	O
second-team	O
Big	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
along	O
with	O
Tyvon	B-PER
Branch	I-PER
.	O

This	O
is	O
often	O
not	O
the	O
case	O
(	O
see	O
conformity	B-ORG
)	O
.	O

Blue	B-ORG
Grass	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
—	O
Lexington	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kentucky	I-LOC

They	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
1943	O
and	O
had	O
five	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
West	B-ORG
Hartford	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
CT	I-ORG
,	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
.	O

**	O
Coastline	O
:	O
Indian	B-LOC
Ocean	I-LOC
185.2	O
km	O

