It	O
also	O
borders	O
the	O
Czech	B-LOC
Republic	I-LOC
.	O

'	O
''	O
Iván	B-PER
Silva	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Priscilla	B-PER
Susan	I-PER
Bury	I-PER

Dębina	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Prudnik	I-LOC
County	I-LOC

Ordinary	B-ORG
language	I-ORG
philosophy	I-ORG

Baker	B-ORG
Bowl	I-ORG
–	O
Philadelphia	B-LOC
,	O
Pennsylvania	B-LOC
(	O
1887–1938	O
)	O
