'	O
''	O
New	B-ORG
Zealand	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
–	O
Martin	B-PER
Guptill	I-PER
,	O
Roneel	B-PER
Hira	I-PER
,	O
Tim	B-PER
Southee	I-PER
,	O
Todd	B-PER
Astle	I-PER
,	O
Colin	B-PER
Munro	I-PER
and	O
Hamish	B-PER
Bennett	I-PER

:	O
:	O
:	O
SE331	O
Västerbotten	B-LOC
County	I-LOC

John	B-PER
Torchetti	I-PER
(	O
interim	O
)	O
:	O
2006	O

South	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Campus	I-ORG

``	O
Crazy	B-ORG
''	O
by	O
Gnarls	B-ORG
Barkley	I-ORG

In	O
2005	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
signed	O
by	O
San	B-ORG
Marino	I-ORG
Calcio	I-ORG
.	O

Empress	B-PER
Dowager	I-PER
Ma	I-PER
(	I-PER
Southern	I-PER
Ming	I-PER
)	I-PER

Jia	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Iran	I-LOC

''	O
Syncopacma	B-LOC
polychromella	I-LOC
''	O
