Rodrigo	B-PER
Mora	I-PER
—	O
River	B-ORG
Plate	I-ORG
(	O
E	O
)	O

Game	B-PER
of	I-PER
Thrones	I-PER

'	O
''	O
Rede	B-ORG
Globo	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Puerto	B-LOC
del	I-LOC
Rosario	I-LOC
