Dar	B-LOC
Gol-e	I-LOC
Seyyed	I-LOC
Hasan	I-LOC

The	O
first	O
of	O
these	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
substantial	O
,	O
identifiable	O
body	O
of	O
work	O
was	O
José	B-PER
Nicolás	I-PER
de	I-PER
la	I-PER
Escalera	I-PER
(	O
1734	O
–	O
1804	O
)	O
.	O

''	O
Desmia	B-LOC
decemmaculalis	I-LOC
''	O

Falco	B-ORG
peregrinus	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Peregrine	B-LOC
falcon	I-LOC
)	O
-	O
LC	O

Cummings	B-ORG
Jewish	I-ORG
Centre	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Seniors	I-ORG

Je	B-ORG
m'voyais	I-ORG
déjà	I-ORG
''	O
–	O
Charles	B-PER
Aznavour	I-PER

Juan	B-PER
de	I-PER
Zurbarán	I-PER

*Church	O
of	O
Our	O
Lady-at-the-Pool	O
in	O
Tienen	B-LOC
(	O
1358–1375	O
)	O

Paul-Martin	B-PER
Gallocher	I-PER
de	I-PER
Lagalisserie	I-PER

Buckley	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
forest	I-LOC
falcon	I-LOC
