``	O
Here	B-ORG
Is	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
News	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Electric	B-ORG
Light	I-ORG
Orchestra	I-ORG
cover	O
)	O
–	O
3:52	O

'	O
''	O
Massimo	B-PER
Luongo	I-PER
''	O
'	O

Clonostachys	B-LOC
rosea	I-LOC
f.	I-LOC
rosea	I-LOC
