George	B-PER
Bernard	I-PER
Shaw	I-PER
(	O
1856–1950	O
)	O

Raymond	B-PER
Riotte	I-PER
(	O
FRA	B-LOC
)	O

''	O
One	B-ORG
Day	I-ORG
at	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Time	I-ORG
''	O

We	B-ORG
Are	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Champions	I-ORG
''	O

Alexandre	B-LOC
(	I-LOC
cratère	I-LOC
)	I-LOC
