The	B-PER
2nd	I-PER
Earl	I-PER
of	I-PER
Suffolk	I-PER
15	O
June	O
1626	O
–	O
3	O
June	O
1640	O

Roman	B-LOC
Catholic	I-LOC
Diocese	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Birmingham	I-LOC
in	I-LOC
Alabama	I-LOC

Ashot	B-PER
I	I-PER
of	I-PER
Iberia	I-PER

He	O
moved	O
to	O
Alma	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wisconsin	I-LOC
in	O
1855	O
.	O

Douglas	B-PER
Rain	I-PER
,	O
''Master	O
Builder	O
''	O

Central	B-ORG
Election	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
Taiwan	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

Her	O
works	O
were	O
exhibited	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	B-ORG
Academy	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Art	I-ORG
between	O
1852	O
and	O
1865	O
.	O

Hinesville	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Georgia	I-LOC
–	O
$	O
14,300	O

It	O
was	O
released	O
under	O
Universal	B-ORG
Records	I-ORG
on	O
early	O
September	O
2007	O
.	O
