Owl	B-PER
Eyes	I-PER
–	O
``	O
Pumped	B-ORG
Up	I-ORG
Kicks	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
Foster	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
People	I-ORG
)	O

Madison	B-ORG
Township	I-ORG
,	O
Lac	B-LOC
qui	I-LOC
Parle	I-LOC
County	I-LOC

Lincoln	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
sparrow	I-LOC
,	O
''Melospiza	O
lincolnii	O
''	O

Pat	B-PER
McAfee	I-PER
–	O
Also	O
played	O
soccer	B-ORG
at	O
West	B-ORG
Virginia	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
.	O
