Mary	B-PER
Wollstonecraft	I-PER
(	O
1759–1797	O
)	O

''	O
Ikaw	B-ORG
Lang	I-ORG
Ang	I-ORG
Mamahalin	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2001–2002	O
)	O

Estasyong	B-ORG
Kamuning	I-ORG
ng	I-ORG
MRT	I-ORG

1997	O
–	O
Toshiro	B-PER
Mifune	I-PER
,	O
Chinese-Japanese	O
actor	O
and	O
producer	O
(	O
b	O
.	O

Saint	B-LOC
Kitts	I-LOC
and	I-LOC
Nevis	I-LOC

Lungsod	B-LOC
ng	I-LOC
Florencia	I-LOC
