It	O
is	O
developed	O
by	O
Turn	B-ORG
10	I-ORG
Studios	I-ORG
and	O
published	O
by	O
Microsoft	B-ORG
Studios	I-ORG
.	O

''	O
Cheirodon	B-LOC
mitopterus	I-LOC
''	O

Valentina	B-PER
Marchei	I-PER
/	O
Ondřej	B-PER
Hotárek	I-PER

Marie	B-PER
Jeanne	I-PER
Baptiste	I-PER
of	I-PER
Savoy-Nemours	I-PER

Chichester	B-PER
Parkinson-Fortescue	I-PER
,	I-PER
1st	I-PER
Baron	I-PER
Carlingford	I-PER
4	O
September	O
1873	O
–	O
1892	O

Jonesboro	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Arkansas	I-LOC

It	O
was	O
established	O
in	O
1982	O
with	O
funding	O
from	O
the	O
John	B-ORG
D.	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Catherine	I-ORG
T.	I-ORG
MacArthur	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
under	O
the	O
leadership	O
of	O
James	B-PER
Gustave	I-PER
Speth	I-PER
.	O

===	O
Xzibit	B-PER
–	O
Man	B-ORG
vs.	I-ORG
Machine	I-ORG
''	O
===	O

Two	B-LOC
Rivers	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Wisconsin	I-LOC
,	O
U.S	B-ORG
.	I-ORG
