'	O
''	O
Lyndon	B-PER
B.	I-PER
Johnson	I-PER
''	O
'August	O
27	O
,	O
1908	O
–	O
January	O
22	O
,	O
1973	O
(	O
aged	O
64	O
)	O

Inés	B-PER
ng	I-PER
Bohemia	I-PER

Santo	B-LOC
Tome	I-LOC
at	I-LOC
Prinsipe	I-LOC

Pangasiwaan	B-ORG
ng	I-ORG
Segurong	I-ORG
Sosyal	I-ORG
