Ardrossan]]	O
,	O
)	O
Strathcona	B-LOC
County	I-LOC

He	O
is	O
a	O
founding	O
Associate	O
Artist	O
of	O
The	B-ORG
Civilians	I-ORG
.	O

East	B-LOC
St.	I-LOC
Louis	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Illinois	I-LOC

Billy	B-PER
Gilbert	I-PER
,	O
2B	O
,	O
1908-1909	O

In	O
1943	O
,	O
he	O
played	O
alongside	O
Gregory	B-PER
Peck	I-PER
in	O
the	O
play	O
''Sons	O
and	O
Soldiers	O
''	O
.	O

*2012	O
Bad	B-ORG
Girls	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
[Oxygen]	O
