Assemblyman	O
Peter	B-PER
J.	I-PER
Barnes	I-PER
III	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O

was	O
a	O
village	B-ORG
located	O
in	O
Ito	B-LOC
District	I-LOC
,	O
Wakayama	B-LOC
Prefecture	I-LOC
,	O
Japan	B-LOC
.	O

Jean	B-PER
De	I-PER
Briac	I-PER
-	O
Shopkeeper	O

'	O
''	O
Marianne	B-PER
Thieme	I-PER
''	O
'	O

*1982	O
Armed	B-ORG
Forces	I-ORG
Staff	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
,	O
Norfolk	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Virginia	I-LOC

)	O
who	O
emigrated	O
from	O
Ennis	B-LOC
,	O
County	B-LOC
Clare	I-LOC
,	O
Ireland	B-LOC
.	O

Old	B-LOC
Crow	I-LOC
(	O
Vuntut	B-ORG
Gwitchin	I-ORG
First	I-ORG
Nation	I-ORG
)	O

''	O
Sultanate	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Rûm	I-ORG
''	O
'	O
–	O
Kilij	B-PER
Arslan	I-PER
I	I-PER
(	O
1092–1107	O
)	O

The	B-ORG
Phone	I-ORG
Co-op	I-ORG
