Same	B-ORG
Trailer	I-ORG
Different	I-ORG
Park	I-ORG
''	O
(	O
2013	O
)	O

Wachenheim	B-ORG
an	I-ORG
der	I-ORG
Weinstraße	I-ORG
(	O
Rhl.-Pf	O
.	O

William	B-PER
McKinley	I-PER
was	O
born	O
in	O
Niles	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ohio	I-LOC
,	O
in	O
1843	O
.	O
