East	B-LOC
Brunswick	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
New	I-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC
.	O

Recorded	O
by	O
Fats	B-PER
Waller	I-PER
.	O

Fountain	B-LOC
Hills	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Arizona	I-LOC

Bruce	B-PER
Springsteen	I-PER
—	O
``	O
Tunnel	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Love	I-ORG
''	O

Devils	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Daily	I-ORG
Journal	I-ORG
''	O
of	O
Devils	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
North	I-LOC
Dakota	I-LOC

They	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
playoff	O
against	O
Belgium	B-ORG
,	O
drawing	O
1–1	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
leg	O
then	O
losing	O
2–1	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
leg	O
.	O

--	O
-	O
Independent	B-LOC
State	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Samoa	I-LOC

Hawkshead	B-ORG
Grammar	I-ORG
School	I-ORG

Anna	B-PER
Sforza	I-PER
(	O
1476–1497	O
)	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
Alfonso	B-ORG
I	I-ORG
d'Este	I-ORG

He	O
received	O
151	O
votes	O
(	O
0.76	O
%	O
)	O
,	O
finishing	O
fourth	O
against	O
Liberal	B-ORG
candidate	O
Gerard	B-PER
Kennedy	I-PER
.	O
