Magnificent	B-LOC
snake	I-LOC
eel	I-LOC

2005	O
:	O
Stephen	B-PER
Edgar	I-PER

Oh	B-ORG
!	I-ORG
Gravity	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
''	O

Hertford	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	O
Ahoskie	B-LOC

PS1491	O
by	O
John	B-PER
Tesh	I-PER

In	O
the	O
past	O
,	O
students	O
have	O
studied	O
,	O
served	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
in	O
England	B-LOC
,	O
Sweden	B-LOC
,	O
Australia	B-LOC
,	O
New	B-LOC
Zealand	I-LOC
,	O
Brazil	B-LOC
,	O
South	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
,	O
Nepal	B-LOC
,	O
Costa	B-LOC
Rica	I-LOC
,	O
Mexico	B-LOC
,	O
Ghana	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
more	O
.	O

Electorate	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Württemberg	I-LOC

VM91	O
:	O
Đắk	B-LOC
Nông	I-LOC
Province	I-LOC

'	O
''	O
With	O
Bob	B-PER
Cooper	I-PER
''	O
'	O

``	O
Keep	B-ORG
A-Knockin	I-ORG
'	I-ORG
''	O
Little	B-PER
Richard	I-PER
