Deputy-mayor	O
of	O
Massy	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Essonne	I-LOC
,	O
1983–1995	O
.	O

In	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
Marc	B-PER
Surer	I-PER
prevailed	O
for	O
the	O
works	O
.	O

El	B-ORG
Fureidis	I-ORG
in	O
Montecito	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
California	I-LOC
,	O
1906	O

Madison	B-ORG
Township	I-ORG
,	O
Lac	B-LOC
qui	I-LOC
Parle	I-LOC
County	I-LOC

Chester	B-PER
C.	I-PER
Thompson	I-PER
(	O
D	O
)	O

Deputy	B-ORG
Prime	I-ORG
Minister	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
United	I-ORG
Kingdom	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Lindsay	B-PER
Hassett	I-PER
''	O
'	O

His	O
widow	O
remarried	O
in	O
1856	O
to	O
John	B-PER
Weld-Forester	I-PER
,	I-PER
2nd	I-PER
Baron	I-PER
Forester	I-PER
,	O
was	O
widowed	O
again	O
in	O
1873	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
1894	O
.	O

A]]	O
)	O
'	O
''	O
Olympiakos	B-ORG
Nicosia	I-ORG
''	O
'	O

Bridgewater	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Vermont	I-LOC
