Lamb	B-LOC
's	I-LOC
Conduit	I-LOC
Field	I-LOC

They	O
arrived	O
on	O
May	O
22	O
,	O
1870	O
,	O
and	O
along	O
with	O
Henry	B-ORG
Howell	I-ORG
helped	O
settle	O
Fish	B-LOC
Haven	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Idaho	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
he	O
later	O
served	O
as	O
Bishop	B-ORG
.	O

Bismarck	B-ORG
Civic	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
,	O
Bismarck	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
North	I-LOC
Dakota	I-LOC

Steven	B-PER
van	I-PER
Herwijck	I-PER

Communes	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
Eure	I-LOC
department	I-LOC

Sharaud	B-PER
Curry	I-PER
(	O
3.5	O
)	O

Amit	B-PER
Kumar	I-PER
,	O
Kavita	B-PER
Krishnamurthy	I-PER

Lesley-Anne	B-PER
Down	I-PER
-	O
Georgina	B-ORG
Worsley	I-ORG

'	O
''	O
Flow	O
''	O
'	O
(	O
Ft.	O
Plan	B-ORG
B	I-ORG
)	O
(	O
2008	O
)	O

Universidad	B-ORG
del	I-ORG
Norte	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Colombia	I-ORG
