Hematite	B-LOC
Township	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Michigan	I-LOC

In	O
the	O
2006	B-ORG
PDC	I-ORG
World	I-ORG
Darts	I-ORG
Championship	I-ORG
,	O
he	O
defeated	O
Steve	B-PER
Maish	I-PER
in	O
the	O
first	O
round	O
,	O
but	O
narrowly	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
round	O
to	O
Peter	B-PER
Manley	I-PER
.	O

2006–07	B-LOC
Real	I-LOC
Madrid	I-LOC
C.F.	I-LOC
season	I-LOC
