David	B-PER
Hudson	I-PER
,	O
lawyer	O
and	O
writer	O

Léopold	B-ORG
II	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Belgium	I-ORG
(	O
1980	O
)	O

Adapted	O
in	O
1947	O
from	O
a	O
play	O
by	O
Ferenc	B-PER
Molnár	I-PER
;	O
not	O
produced	O

Chris	B-PER
Adcock	I-PER
/	O
Andrew	B-PER
Ellis	I-PER
''	O
(	O
First	O
Round	O
)	O

San	B-LOC
Francisco	I-LOC
–	O
'	O
''	O
KGO-TV	B-ORG
7	O
''	O
'	O

In	O
1991	O
,	O
the	O
headquarters	O
shifted	O
to	O
Naples	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Florida	I-LOC
.	O

''Téléfoot	O
''	O
by	O
Thierry	B-PER
Roland	I-PER

Gate	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
China	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Beijing	I-ORG

This	O
species	O
is	O
only	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Caribbean	B-LOC
Sea	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
abundant	O
.	O

''	O
The	B-ORG
Heart	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Chicago	I-ORG
1967–1998	I-ORG
Volume	I-ORG
II	I-ORG
''	O

List	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
number-one	I-ORG
R	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
B	I-ORG
albums	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
1999	I-ORG
(	I-ORG
U.S	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
)	I-ORG

(	O
A	O
)	O
Recorded	O
at	O
Rockfield	B-LOC
Studios	I-LOC
,	O
1982	O
