Commonwealth	B-ORG
Stadium	I-ORG
,	O
Lexington	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Kentucky	I-LOC

:1st	O
Stage	O
4	O
Giro	B-ORG
d'Italia	I-ORG
,	O
Enrico	B-PER
Battaglin	I-PER
